<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Object Tracker</string>

    <!-- Content Descriptions -->
    <string name="product_icon_content_description">Product Icon in an ImageView</string>

    <!-- Button Texts -->
    <string name="start_tracking">Start Tracking</string>
    <string name="preferences">Preferences</string>
    <string name="view_recordings">View Recordings</string>

    <!-- Camera UI Text -->
    <string name="timestamp">0:00:00</string>

    <!-- Flash popup menu -->
    <string name="flash_state_off">Off</string>
    <string name="flash_state_on">On</string>

    <!-- Freeze button -->
    <string name="freeze_enabled">Frozen</string>
    <string name="freeze_disabled">Live</string>

    <string name="set_color">Color</string>
    <string name="mode">Mode</string>
    <string name="manual_tracking">Manual Tracking</string>
    <string name="automatic_tracking">Automatic Tracking</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>


    <!-- Help Dialog -->
    <string name="help_dialog_manual_tracking">Manual Tracking</string>
    <string name="help_dialog_automatic_tracking">Automatic Tracking</string>
    <string name="help_dialog_manual_tracking_desc">
        Manual tracking is the simplest type of tracking mode this app offers. Simply select the
        "Manual Tracking" option by clicking on the MODE button. After pressing the record button, you
        can then click on the object that you wish to track, every 3-5 seconds.
        \n\nUpon each click, the coordinates of the touch will be appended to a .yml data file, along with the time and
        frame number of the touch. A circle will be overlayed on the touch location*. Along with the recording file,
        the data file allows for offline tracking using your favourite external tools.
    </string>

    <string name="help_dialog_automatic_tracking_desc">
        Automatic tracking uses a more advanced technique called "template matching". When selecting
        this method, the user will be presented with an option to select a template of the image
        that they wish to track. Upon selecting the template and pressing record, template matching
        uses a method that searches the entire image frame for the template specified by the user.
        Upon finding a closest match, a bounding box will be drawn around the location of the detected
        object*.
        \n\n To select a template for template matching:
        \n *Instructions on how to select template here*

        \n\n\n\n\n*You can change the circle overlay color by tapping the icon labelled \"Color\".

    </string>
</resources>
